[
  {
    "id": "01",
    "question": "What did Joey buy for Chandler because they're best friends?",
    "options": ["pizza", "framed picture of a chimp", "watch", "bracelet"],
    "answer": "watch"
  },
  {
    "id": "02",
    "question": "What address does Chandler give Janis to write to?",
    "options": [
      "46 Central Park Road, New York",
      "15, Yemen Road, Yemen",
      "16 Pennsylvania Avenue",
      "64 Maddison Square Gardens"
    ],
    "answer": "15, Yemen Road, Yemen"
  },
  {
    "id": "03",
    "question": "Where do Rachel and Ross go on their first date?",
    "options": [
      "Cinema",
      "Ross's Museum",
      "Central Perk",
      "The Empire State Building"
    ],
    "answer": "Ross's Museum"
  },
  {
    "id": "04",
    "question": "What's the first thing Ross says at the beginning of the opening episode?",
    "options": [
      "Has anyone seen my fossil collection?",
      "How YOU doin'?",
      "Coul I be wearing any more clothes?",
      "Hi..."
    ],
    "answer": "Hi..."
  },
  {
    "id": "05",
    "question": "What is the name of Joey’s acting agent?",
    "options": ["Andrea", "Estelle", "Martha", "Carole"],
    "answer": "Estelle"
  },
  {
    "id": "06",
    "question": "Which job did Rachel’s fiancé Barry Farber do?",
    "options": ["Lawyer", "Plumber", "Orthodondist", "Journalist"],
    "answer": "Orthodondist"
  },
  {
    "id": "07",
    "question": "Phoebe dated a scientist called David. In which Belarus city did he work?",
    "options": ["Minsk", "Grodno", "Mogilev", "Pinsk"],
    "answer": "Minsk"
  },
  {
    "id": "08",
    "question": "Phoebe has a twin sister. What's her name?",
    "options": ["Scarlett", "Ursula", "Sharon", "Rita"],
    "answer": "Ursula"
  },
  {
    "id": "09",
    "question": "In which city is Friends set?",
    "options": ["Los Angeles", "New York City", "Miami", "Seattle"],
    "answer": "New York City"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "What does Joey never share?",
    "options": ["Books", "Information", "Food", "DVDs"],
    "answer": "Food"
  }
]
